NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Boards of Education: Remsen through Rhineckill (Box 196)
  - Rhinecliff Union Free School District, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - Rhinebeck, 1987-1992 (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Rhinecliff UFSD, 1991-1996 (Box 196, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Richburg through Ripley (Box 197)
  - Richburg, 1972-1987 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Richburg - Sch. Dist., 1988-1995 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Richburg, 1968-1984 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Richfield Springs, 1989-1998 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Richfield, 1976-1996 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Richburg, 1987-1989 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Richfield, 1970-1981 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Richfield, 1981-1983 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Richfield Springs - Sch. Dist., 1993-1996 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Richmondville, 1972-1974 (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Richmondville #1 School District, 1990-1992 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Richmondville CSD, 1979-1982 (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - Richmondville, 1982-1984 (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Rider Street Sch., 1969-1971 (Box 197, Folder 14)
  - Ridge Street School, 1971-1975 (Box 197, Folder 15)
  - Ridge Street, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 16)
  - Ripley, 1980-1987 (Box 197, Folder 17)
  - Ripley, 1989-1995 (Box 197, Folder 18)
  - Ripley - Sch. Dist., 1999 (Box 197, Folder 19)
  - Ripley, 1973-1974 (Box 197, Folder 20)
  - Ripley, 1970-1982 (Box 197, Folder 21)
- Boards of Education: Riverhead through Rockland (Box 198)
  - Riverhead, 1969-1981 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Sch. Dist. - Riverhead C.S.D., 1991 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Riverhead, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Riverhead, 1970-1986 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Riverhead, 1988-1991 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Rochester, 1971-1988 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Rochester, 1968-2000 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Rochester, 1984-2000 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Rochester, 1975-1980 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Sch. Dist. - Rochester, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Rochester, 1970-1973 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Rockland, 1979-1992 (Box 198, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Rockville through Rome (Box 199)
  - Sch. Dist. - Rockville Centre, 1991-1994 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Rockville, 1968-1982 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Rockville, 1971-1982 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Rockville Centre, 1980-2000 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Rockville Centre, 1972-2000 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Rocky Point, 1970-1983 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Rocky Point, 1999-2002 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Rocky Point, 1972 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Rocky Point, 1982-1996 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Rocky Point, 1986-1989 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Roeliff Jansen, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Rome, 1974-1999 (Box 199, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. - Rome P.S., 1998-2001 (Box 199, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Rome through Romulous (Box 200)
  - Rome, 1970-1987 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Rome, 1971-1981 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Rome, 1968-1981 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Rome City, 1990-1998 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Romulas, 1969-1993 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Romulas, 1970-1982 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Romulus, 1989-1998 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Romulus, 1990-1994 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Romulus, 1971-1993 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Romulus - Sch. Dist., 1986-1991 (Box 200, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Rondout through Roslyn (Box 201)
  - Rondout, 1972-1982 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Rondout Valley School, 1980-1993 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Rondout, 1985-1991 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Rondout Valley, 1968-1984 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Rondout Valley - Sch. Dist., 1986-1996 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Rondout Valley, 1972-1979 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, 1977-2005 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt - Sch. Dist., 1991 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, 1984-1989 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Roscoe, 1992-2006 (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Roscoe, 1978-1984 (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Roscoe CSD, 1988-1991 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Roscoe, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Roslyn, 1970-1975 (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Roslyn - Sch. Dist., 1989-1994 (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Roslyn, 1983-1987 (Box 201, Folder 17)
  - Roslyn, 1969-1989 (Box 201, Folder 18)
- Boards of Education: Roslyn through Royalton-Hartland (Box 202)
  - Roslyn, 1969-1988 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Roslyn, 1993-2009 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Roslyn, 1968-2000 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Rotterdam - Draper, 1975-1994 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Sch. Dist. - Rotterdam - Mohonasen, 1991-2005 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Roxbury, 1968-1998 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Sch. Dist. - Roxbury C.S., 1997-2002 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Roxbury, 1988-1992 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Roxbury, 1990-1997 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Royalton - Hartland, 1973-1984 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Royalton - Hartland, 1977-1983 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - Royalton - Hartland - Sch. Dist., 1989 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Royalton - Hartford, 1969-1991 (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Royalton - Hartland, 1979-1992 (Box 202, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Rush-Henrietta through Rye (Box 203)
  - Sch. Dist. - Rush - Henrietta, 1988-1992 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Rush - Henrietta, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Rush - Henrietta, 1969-1982 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Rush - Henrietta, 1995-2007 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Rush - Henretta, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Rush - Henrietta, 1975-1982 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Rush - Henrietta, 1966-1997 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Rushford, 1975-1983 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Rushford - Sch. Dist., 1986-1992 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Rushford, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Rushford, 1973-1992 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Rushford Central School Dist. + the CSEA, 1971-1981 (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - Rushford, 1987-1989 (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Rye, 1972-1990 (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - Rye, 1970-1974 (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - Rye, 1995-2000 (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - Rye - Sch. Dist., 1992-1995 (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - Rye, 1987-1990 (Box 203, Folder 18)
  - Rye, 1985-1997 (Box 203, Folder 19)
- Boards of Education: Rye Neck through St. Johnsville (Box 204)
  - Rye Neck, 1972-1982 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Rye Neck - Sch. Dist., 1980-1985 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Rye Neck, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Rye Neck, 1979-1986 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Sachem, 1969-1978 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Sachem, 1986-1987 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Sch. Dist. - Sachem C.S., 1990-1996 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Sachem, 1969-1977 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Sachem, 1996-2000 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Sackets Harbor, 1978-2000 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Sackets Harbor, 1990 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Sackets Harbor, 1994-1997 (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Sag Harbor, 1980-1990 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Sag Harbor, 1990-1993 (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Sag Harbor, 1970-1972 (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - Sag Harbor UFSD #5, 1989 (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - St. Christopher (Jennie), 1981-1994 (Box 204, Folder 17)
  - St. Christophers, 1989 (Box 204, Folder 18)
  - Saint Johnsville, 1988-1992 (Box 204, Folder 19)
  - St. Johnsville, 1979-1993 (Box 204, Folder 20)
- Boards of Education: St. Johnsville through Salamanca (Box 205)
  - Saint Johnsville, 1984-1985 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - St. Johnsville Red Hook - Sch. Dist., 2002 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - St. Johnsville, 1985-1997 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Saint Lawrence, 1980-1990 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - St. Lawrence, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Sch. Dist. - St. Lawrence, 2002-2004 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - St. Lawrence, 1968-1982 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - St. Lawrence, 1969-1975 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Saint Lawrence, 1972-2000 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Sag Harbor, 1987-1990 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - St. Lawrence, 1988-1997 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Saint Regis Falls, 1968-1970 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - Saint Regis Falls, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - Sch. Dist. - St. Regis Falls, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - St. Regis, 1986-1990 (Box 205, Folder 15)
  - Saint Regis Falls, 1972-1998 (Box 205, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Salamanca through Sandy Creek (Box 206)
  - Sch. Dist. - Salamanca, 1992-1995 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Salamanca, 1969-1970 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Salamanca, 1971-1995 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Salamanca, 1976-1984 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Salamanca, 1989-2004 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Salamanca, 1986-1989 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Salem, 1973-1986 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Salem, 1987-1999 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Salem Central School District, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Salmon River, 1982-1988 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Salmon River Sch. Dist., 1990-1996 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Salmon River, 1985-1992 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Salmon River, 1972 (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Sandy Creek, 1971-1983 (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Sandy Creek, 1992-1996 (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - Sandy Creek, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Sandy Creek, 1986-1994 (Box 206, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Sandy Creek through Saratoga Springs (Box 207)
  - Sandy Creek, 1969-1983 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Saranac, 1970-1978 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Saranac, 1968-1999 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Saranac, 1974 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Saranac School District, 1998-2001 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Saranac, 1986-1994 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Saranac Lake, 1969-2005 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Saranac Lake, 1970-1980 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Saranac Lake - Sch. Dist., 1998-2002 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Saranac Lake, 1974-1989 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Saranac Lake, 1992 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga, 1982-1993 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga Springs C.S.D., 1979 (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga Springs, 1985-1997 (Box 207, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Saratoga Springs through Savona (Box 208)
  - Saratoga Springs, 1980-1999 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Sauquoit, 1990-1998 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Saugerties, 1986-1994 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Sch. Dist. - Saugerties, 1996-2000 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Saugerties, 1963-1972 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Saugerties, 1996-2000 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Sauquoit, 1968-1986 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Sauquoit, 1968-1989 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Saugerties, 1989-2001 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - Sch. Dist. - Sauquoit Valley, 1993-1995 (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Sauquoit Valley (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - Sauquoit Valley, 1986-1998 (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - Savona, 1970-1983 (Box 208, Folder 13)
  - Savona School District, 1988-1990 (Box 208, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Savona through Scarsdale (Box 209)
  - Savona, 1975-1982 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Sayville, 1971-1989 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Sayville, 1970-1994 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Sch. Dist. - Sayville, 1996-2001 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Sayville, 1968-1983 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Sayville, 1986-1993 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Scarsdale, 1968-1970 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Scarsdale - School District, 1992-1995 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Scarsdale, 1971-1983 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Scarsdale, 1989-1992 (Box 209, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Schalmont through Schenectady (Box 210)
  - Schalmont, 1983-2001 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Schalmont - Sch. Dist., 1991-1994 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Schalmont, 1980 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Schamont, 1971-1994 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady, 1972-2007 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady, 1976-1986 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Sch. Dist. - Schenectady, 1993-1998 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady, 1978-1985 (Box 210, Folder 8)
- Boards of Education: Schenevus through Schoharie (Box 211)
  - Schenevus, 1984-1997 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Schenevus, 1963-1990 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Shenendehowa, 1980 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Schenevus, 1988-1994 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Schodack, 1980-1984 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Schodack CS, 1993-1995 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Schodack, 1971-1982 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Schodack, 1970-1981 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Shodack, 1972-1992 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Schoharie, 1971-1997 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Schorie, 1987-1990 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Schoharie, 1968-2003 (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Schoharie, 1974-1977 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Sch. Dist. - Schoharie, 1991-1995 (Box 211, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Schroon through Seaford (Box 212)
  - Schroon Lake, 1968-2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Sch. Dist. - Schroon C.S., 1998-2001 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Schroon Lake (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Schroon Lake, 1978-2007 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Schroon Lake Central, 1984-1998 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Schuylerville, 1968-1972 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Schuylerville, 1968-1995 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Schuylerville, 1969-1977 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Schuylerville, 1973-2002 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Scio - Allentown, 1972-1983 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Scio - Allentown CS, 1999-2002 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Scio, 1979-1997 (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. - Scotia- Glenville C.S., 1978-2000 (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - Scotia - Glenville, 1969-1973 (Box 212, Folder 14)
  - Scotia - Glenville, 1968-1973 (Box 212, Folder 15)
  - Seaford, 1968-2006 (Box 212, Folder 16)
  - Sch. Dist. - Seaford, 1990-1994 (Box 212, Folder 17)
  - Seaford, 1970-1994 (Box 212, Folder 18)
- Boards of Education: Seaford through Sewanhaka (Box 213)
  - Seaford, 1968-1988 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Seaford, 1975-1983 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Seaford, 1969-1993 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Seneca Falls, 1981-1991 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Seneca Falls - Sch. Dist., 1992-1997 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Seneca Falls, 1971-1973 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Seneca Falls, 1968-1992 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Sewanhaka, 1970-1972 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Sewanhaka, 1980-1998 (Box 213, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Sewahaka through Sherburn-Earlville (Box 214)
  - Sewanhaka, 1969-1985 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Sewanhaka CSD, 1998-2003 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Sharon Springs, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Sharon Springs #1 School District, 1995-1999 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Sharon Springs, 1974-1981 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Sharon Springs, 1977-1995 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Shelter Island, 1977-1995 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Shelter Island, 1977-1991 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - Shelter Island, 1974 (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Shenendehowa, 1968-2006 (Box 214, Folder 10)
  - Shenenehowa, 1973-1978 (Box 214, Folder 11)
  - Sch. Dist. - Shenendehowa, 1991-2003 (Box 214, Folder 12)
  - Shenendehowa, 1971-1993 (Box 214, Folder 13)
  - Sherburne - Earlville, 1970-1980 (Box 214, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Sherburne-Earlville through Silver Creek (Box 215)
  - Sherburne - Earlville, 1972-1987 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Sch. Dist. - Sherburne - Earlville C.S., 1992-1995 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Sherburne - Ea rlville, 1974 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Sherman, 1977-1996 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Sherman - Sch. Dist., 1994-1996 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Sherman, 1980-2000 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Sherman, 1973 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Sherman, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Shoreham, 1969-1974 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Shoreham, 1981-1986 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Shoreham, 1970-1972 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - Shoreham - Sch. Dist., 1991-1994 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - Shoreham - Wading River, 1991-1996 (Box 215, Folder 13)
  - Sidney, 1972-2002 (Box 215, Folder 14)
  - Sch. Dist. - Sidney, 1991-1994 (Box 215, Folder 15)
  - Sidney, 1975-1988 (Box 215, Folder 16)
  - Sidney, 1990-1993 (Box 215, Folder 17)
  - Sidney, 1972 (Box 215, Folder 18)
  - Silver Creek, 1970-1999 (Box 215, Folder 19)
- Boards of Education: Silver Creek through Smithtown (Box 216)
  - Silver Creek - Sch. Dist., 1995-1998 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Silver Creek, 1974-1983 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Silver Creek, 1970-2006 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Skaneateles, 1969-1986 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Skaneateles, 1986-1990 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Sch. Dist. - Skaneateles C.S.D., 1994 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Skaneateles, 1972-1982 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Skaneateles, 1989-1993 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Smithtown, 1968-1983 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Smithtown, 1977-1992 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Sch. Dist. - Smithtown S.D., 1997-2003 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Smithtown, 1971-1983 (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Smithtown, 1972-1990 (Box 216, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Sodus through Somers (Box 217)
  - Sodus, 1972 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Sodus - Sch. Dist., 1992-1996 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Sodus, 1984-1986 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Sodus, 1972-1989 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Solvay Union, 1979-1995 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Solvay, 1978-1989 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Solvay S.D., 2002-2007 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Somers, 1969-1994 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Somers - Sch. Dist., 1992-1998 (Box 217, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Somers through South Glens Falls (Box 218)
  - Somers, 1973-1974 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Somers School District, 2001-2005 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - South Berlin, 1994-1995 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - South Colonie, 1969-1975 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Sch. Dist. - So. Colonie C.S., 1998-2004 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - South Colonie, 1970-1995 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - South Colonie, 1970-1991 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - South Colonie Central School District, 2000-2005 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - South Country, 1975-1986 (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - South Country C.S.D., 1991-1996 (Box 218, Folder 10)
  - South Country, 1974 (Box 218, Folder 11)
  - Southern Cayuga, 1971-1980 (Box 218, Folder 12)
  - Southern Cayuga, 1977-1984 (Box 218, Folder 13)
  - Sch. Dist. - So. Glens Falls, 1993-2000 (Box 218, Folder 14)
  - South Glens Falls, 1980 (Box 218, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: South Glens Falls through South Huntington (Box 219)
  - Southern Cayuga, 1968-1989 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - South Glen Falls, 1988-2000 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Southampton, 1991-1997 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Southold Union, 1992-1997 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - South Glens Falls, 1971-1983 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - South Huntington Union, 1973-1984 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - South Hampton, 1971 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - South Glens Falls, 1968-1976 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - South Huntington, 1968-1978 (Box 219, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: South Huntington through South Kortright (Box 220)
  - South Huntington, 1989-2004 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - South Huntington, 1971-1979 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - South Huntington UFSD, 1985-1995 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - South Huntington, 1986-1991 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - South Jefferson, 1975-2008 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - South Jefferson, 1972-1979 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - So. Jefferson - Sch. Dist., 2001-2004 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - South Jefferson, 1982-1993 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - South Jefferson, 1974-1989 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - South Kortright, 1973-1991 (Box 220, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: South Kortright through South Orangetown (Box 221)
  - Sch. Dist. South Kortright, 1991-2003 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - South Kortright, 1972-1991 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - South Lewis, 1994-2002 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - South Manor - Sch. Dist., 1991-1997 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - South Lewis, 1971-1977 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - South Lewis, 1989-1997 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - South Manor, 1974-1975 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - South Manor, 1969-1986 (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - South Manor, 1969-1988 (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Southern Cayuga - Sch. Dist., 1990-1996 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - Southern Cayuga, 1975-1982 (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Southampton, 1980-1993 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. Southold H.S., 1972-1989 (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - So. Orangetown - Sch. Dist., 1995-2007 (Box 221, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: South Orangetown through Southold (Box 222)
  - South Orange town Central, 1976-2002 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - South Otselic, 1976-1977 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - South Seneca, 1974-2003 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - South Seneca - Sch. Dist., 1993-1997 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - South Seneca, 1970-1997 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - South Seneca, 1978-1989 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Southampton, 1971-1994 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Southampton Sch. Dist., 1994-2000 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Southampton, 1969-1988 (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Southern Cayuga - Sch. Dist., 1990-1996 (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - South Cayuga, 1975-1982 (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Southampton, 1980-1993 (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. Southold H.S., 1972-1989 (Box 222, Folder 13)
  - Southold, 1973-1982 (Box 222, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Southold through Spencer Van Etten (Box 223)
  - Southold, 1975-1986 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Southold, 1989 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Southwestern, 1968-1971 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Southwestern, 1970-1983 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Southwestern, 1987-1993 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Southwestern C.S.D. (Jamestown, N.Y.), 1991-1994 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Southwestern, 1969-1985 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Spackenhill, 1968-1969 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Spackenhill, 1970-1973 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Spackenhill, 1970-1973 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Spackenhill - Sch. Dist., 1990-1993 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Spackenhill, 1977-2001 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - Sparkill, 1977 (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - Spencer - Van Etten, 1969-1973 (Box 223, Folder 14)
  - Spencer Van - Etten, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 15)
  - Spencer Van-Etten, 1969-1974 (Box 223, Folder 16)
  - Spencer Van-Etten, 1970-1997 (Box 223, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Spencerport through Springville-Griffith (Box 224)
  - Sch. Dist. - Spencerport, 1992-2002 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Spencerport, 1979-1991 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Spencerport, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Spencerport Central School District, 2005-2008 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Spencerport, 1977-1985 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Spencerport, 1977-1991 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Springfield, 1971-1980 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Springfield CS, 1986-1988 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Springs, 1980-1987 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Springs (East Hampton #4), 1991-1996 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Springville - Griffith, 1975-2003 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - Springville - Griffith, 1981-2005 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - Springville - Griffith Institute - Sch. Dist., 1985-2005 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Springville-Griffith, 1983-1989 (Box 224, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Stamford through Stillwater (Box 225)
  - Stamford - Sch. Dist., 1990-1997 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Stamford, 1969-1990 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Starpoint, 1968-1980 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Sch. Dist. - Starpoint, 1990-1999 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Starpoint, 1969-1972 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Starpoint, 1970-1980 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Starpoint, 1982-1999 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Stillwater, 1970-1988 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Stillwater, 1972 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Stillwater #1 School District, 1987-1989 (Box 225, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Syracuse through Syracuse (Box 226)
  - Stockbridge Valley, 1968-1984 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Stockbridge, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Stockbridge Valley - Sch. Dist., 1996-2003 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Stockbridge, 1992-1997 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Stockbridge, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Stockbridge, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Stratford, 1970-1980 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Leaf, 1979 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Sugar Leaf [Orange County] UFSD, 1990-1992 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Sugar Leaf UFSD, 1979 (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Sullivan West CSD, 1999-2005 (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Susquehanna Valley, 1969-1972 (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Susquehanna Valley, 1976-1997 (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - Susquehanna Valley, 1974 (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Susquehanna Valley, 1993-1998 (Box 226, Folder 15)
  - Sweet Home, 1969-1994 (Box 226, Folder 16)
  - Sweet Home, 1970-1979 (Box 226, Folder 17)
  - Sweet Home - Sch. Dist., 1989-2003 (Box 226, Folder 18)
- Boards of Education: Stockbridge through Sweet Home (Box 227)
  - Sweet Home, 1968-1989 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Sweet Home, 1969-1979 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Sweet Home, 1989-2000 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Sweet Home Central District of Amherst of Tonawanda, 2000-2009 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Sylvan - Verona Beach, 1977-1987 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Sylvan - Verona Beach school District, 1991-1995 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Sylvan - Verona Beach C.S.D., 1979 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Sysoset, 1969-1992 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Syosset - Sch. Dist., 1994-1998 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Syosset, 1983-1991 (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - Syosset, 1968-2001 (Box 227, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Sweet Home through Syossett (Box 228)